看誰來了
Hey look who it is.
施密特
Schmidt.
這位是
And uh?
這是芭芭  她正要走
This is Barb. Barb is leaving.
哦  巴寶  不是那個大象的名字么
Oh, Barb. Like the elephant.
傻貨  那是巴巴
That's Babar, you dum-dum.
芭芭拉  來補點鉀吧
Barbara. A little potassium pick-me-up?
顯然你們昨晚
Since I know sleeping wasn't
可沒怎么睡覺
the main activity of the night.
我們家墻隔音不好  開玩笑啦  墻很厚的
Thin walls. Just kidding. They're very thick.
不過你實在叫得太大聲
You're just so loud!
-你室友好多啊  -特別多  很棒吧
- You have a lot of roommates. - So many of 'em. That's great.
-再見  芭芭  -再見  芭芭
- Bye, Barb. - Bye, Barb.
再見  施密特
Bye, Schmidt.
這都是你這周約的第三個了吧
That was the third piece of nanny
-是不是  -是的
- this week, am I right? - Sure is.
給我也傳授點經驗啊
Little shop talk from someone who's also out there
我也想找一個
trying to crush butt herself.
你都是從哪里
Um, where are you meeting all
找到這些單身美女的啊
these eligible singles, these, uh, elly-sings?
-搖約  -什么
- Dice. - Hmm?
-就跟燃燒者差不多  -搖約和燃燒者
- It's kind of like Tinder. - Dice and Tinder.
我去過那些酒吧  就在市中心  對吧
I've been to those bars. They're downtown, right?
搖約是個約炮軟件
Dice is a dating app.
-約炮軟件  -不是給你用的
- Dating app. - It's not for you.
什么  小施
What? Schmidty.
我也在網上約會過啊
Come on. I've Internet dated before.
發封郵件  然后很激動地
You send an e-mail, you get excited,
等著對方回復
you wait, you get an e-mail back.
-誰發郵件不是這樣啊  -給我見識見識
- You are just describing e-mailing. - Come on.
你要上了搖約準給生吞活剝了
You're gonna get eaten alive on Dice.
-你想看看么  -來嘛
- Do you want to see... - Come on, now.
你想看么...  這就是搖約  過來看
Do you want to see... This is Dice. Come here.
都是瞬間的決定  懂么
It's all about split-second decisions, okay?
你看到對方的照片  向下滑就是喜歡
You see a picture, you swipe down for yes,
-向上滑就是不喜歡  -你怎么這么快
- you swipe up for no. - You're so fast.
直覺  這東西就是靠直覺
Instinct. That's what it's about.
可你壓根沒有
Which you don't have.
我得去好好漱漱口
Now, I'm gonna go do a deep-ass mouthwash.
不要上搖約  杰茜
Don't go on Dice, Jess.
我不會的
I won't.
來看看
Okay, now.
創建新用戶
New account.
我叫"尋歡作樂狂"
I am... Darn Tootin' Fun.
炮炮約起
DTF. (Down to Fuck)
搜同類
Seeks same.
搖約走起
I'm Dicing.
杰茜駕到  第四季第二集
■
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯：小p  持久的菲力  青椒
其實我還真挺喜歡警校的
You know, I'm really enjoying the police academy,
翻譯：毛毛的毛  Aaachi  兮之  許大嘴
但是吧
but, believe it or not,
翻譯：MythCreator  沐頭  CS小明漫畫家
我跟其他學員有點處不來
I am not clicking socially with the other cadets.
-什么  -天啊  -真的假的
- What? - Weird. - Oh, my God.
校對：持久君  麥田守望者
別鬧了
No. That's crazy.
-太令人震驚了  -這我很難理解啊
- That is super shocking news. - I can't wrap my head around that.
時間軸： 糖不甩  chance-coco  后期：MythCreator
真是搞不懂  除了我別人都有小名
That just doesn't add up. Everyone's got a nickname but me.
總監：持久君
-大鳥  -老炮手
- Yo, Swoops! - What up, Gunner?
你好  溫斯頓·貝肖普
Hey, Winston Bishop.
不如你直接去問他們
Why don't you just go ask them
能不能跟他們一起出去玩
if you can hang out with them sometime?
又能糟糕到哪里去
I mean, what's the worst that could happen?
只邀請我自己  哪也太無禮了
Just invite myself? Now, that's just rude.
溫尼·小畢我從小就彬彬有禮
Winnie the Bish wasn't raised to be rude.
幫我留著座  我要去便個便
Now, save my seat. I got to go make a caca.
不敢相信我們要跟警察住一起了
I can't believe we're gonna live with a cop.
我們還能干違法的事嗎
I mean, can we still do illegal things?
-比如說  -我也不知道
- Like... - I don't know,
要是我嗑嗨了什么的
what if I want to get stoned or something?
我還沒嗑嗨過呢
I've actually never gotten stoned before.
-你沒嗨過  -真的假的
- You've never been stoned? - What?
我該趁他沒當上警察之前試一回嗎
Should I do it before he becomes a cop?
-我們可以磕一回  -真的嗎
- We could do this. - Really?
都是成年人  抽點大麻沒事的
We're adults. We can smoke a little weed.
-我們嗑吧  -我有陣子沒嗑藥了
- I think we should do it. - It's been a while.
我學東西很快的
I pick up stuff really quick.
大麻可不是隨便就能學會的
You can't just pick up pot and be good at it.
就像生活中的各種事一樣  孰能生巧
Like everything else in life, it takes practice.
如果把大麻比作鋼琴
Yeah, if pot were a piano,
尼克就是九歲的中國小神童
Nick would be a nine-year-old Chinese girl.
你就交給我吧  包教包會
Daddy's here to take care of you. I'm gonna guide you through it.
我就是你精神導師
I'll be your spiritual guru.
老娘我今天下午也沒事
And mommy's got nothing to do this afternoon,
我去烤點大麻蛋糕
so I'm gonna bake some damn brownies
讓大家都嗨起來
so we can all freak out.
-就這么辦了  -我們要嗨了
- Let's do it. - We're getting stoned?
這簡直就是小屁孩開會啊
This is like watching a meeting of idiot 12-year-olds.
這是什么  什么這么吵
The hell is that? What is that noise?
是你的電話響
Your cellular technology.
都兩年沒人給過我打電話了
I haven't gotten a non-text message in two years.
杰茜
Jess?
我搖了搖
Hey, uh... so, I Diced
結果不錯
and it was great.
但你能來接我一下嗎
but could I get a ride?
你真的不想再跳一會了嗎
You sure you don't want to hop on for a second?
你養狗了嗎  還是說這都是你的
Do you have a dog, or is this all you?
你想聽哪種回答
Which would you prefer?
施密特  你能跟我說句話嗎
Schmidt, will you at least just talk to me, please?
他照片上看著還不錯啊
He looked nice in his picture.
只不過沒照全他的胡子
The frame cut off the bottom of his beard,
所以我怎么會知道他把胡子編成了小辮子
so how was I to know it was braided into a beardy tail?
他找我去他家旁邊的美食廣場
He asked me to the food court near his house.
我覺得很實在  我很喜歡
I thought that was down-to-earth, and I liked that.
可他沒帶錢
He didn't bring any money,
所以我們只能回他的公寓
so we had to go back to his apartment.
他還想給我看他的舊嬰兒服
And also he wanted to show me some of his old baby clothes.
也許我還沒準備好玩搖約
Maybe I'm not ready for Dice.
你就不能幫幫我嗎
Will you just help me, please?
我想重回情場  我必須得...
I want to get back out there. I have to...
我必須得重回情場
I need to get back out there.
我知道自己很容易上當
And I know I'm gullible.
因為人們說的話
'Cause people tell me that,
我沒有理由不相信
and I have no reason not to believe them.
教我玩搖約吧
Teach me to Dice.
這是答應了嗎
Is that a yes?
施密特
Schmidt?
出什么事了
What's happening?
你干什么
Ah! What the hell?
我會教你玩搖約的
I will teach you Dice.
歡迎  早上好
歡迎
Welcome and...
早上好
good morning.
-這里的早上好奇怪  -確實
- It's weird here in the morning. - It is very sad.
在接下來的一千分鐘里
Now, over the next 1,000 minutes,
你對約會的看法將被徹底顛覆
your notions of dating will be challenged.
-杰茜  聽著就好  別記筆記  -我錯了
- Jess, just listen. No notes. - I'm sorry.
桌子上放了筆和筆記本
You put notebooks and pens on the table,
-我還以為  -我明白了
- so I thought... - I totally get it.
杰茜  你很緊張  要喝點水嗎
Look, Jess, you're nervous. Would you like some water?
-謝謝你  -不用
- Oh, thank you. - Of course.
-你人真好...  -千萬別露怯
- That's really nice of... - Never show weakness.
記下來  假如你正在玩搖約
Write that down. Now, you're on Dice
出現了這么個健美男
and this hunk shows up.
哇啦哇啦  我要心動啦
Hubba hubba, Mama in trubba.
別再這樣丟人了好嗎
Don't ever do that again.
-好吧  -你覺得這個人
- Okay. - So you find this man.
長得很有雷神家的氣質
He looks like a Hemsworth,
假設一下
if you will.
他手指下滑  你也一樣
He swipes down, you swipe down,
約好之后  我出現了
you guys set a date. I show up.
你好  我是杰克·斯蒂爾
Hey, how you doing? I'm Jack Steele.
杰克你好
Hi, Jack.
-錯了  -這是我們的禁言蜂鳴器嗎
- Wrong. - Is that our taboo buzzer?
這不重要  我為什么按
Not important. Why did I buzz?
你用完之后能不能放回盒子里
Do you think you could just return it to the box when you're done?
我按的原因是  我長得跟照片完全不一樣
The reason I buzzed is because I look nothing like this person.
你看  他溫柔暖心  甜如陽光
Look at this. There's a sun-kissed sweetie.
而我冷峻滄桑  飽經風霜
I am a rugged Semitic prince.
-我以為在搞角色扮演  -角色扮演
- I thought we were role-playing. - Role-playing?
你覺得這一切都是游戲嗎
What about this feels like a game to you?
找到匹配的了
Ooh, I got a Dice match.
雅各布
Jacob.
他的眼睛真夢幻
He has dreamy eyes.
-這雙美眸比銀行賬戶都有價值  -行了
- Them's joint-bank-account eyes. - Okay,
如果你當著我的面就開始說這種話
if you're saying things like "Dreamy eyes" to my face,
你的教學之路會比里昂王族的音樂事業還要艱辛
we have more work to do than the Kings of Leon.
美國搖滾樂隊  成立于1999年
挺不錯的樂隊
Good band,
但是感覺他們的音樂總是滯步不前
but it feels like they are stuck in one place musically.
我還挺喜歡這人的
Well, I have a good feeling about this guy.
我要約他出來
Okay. I'm gonna ask him out.
你還沒準備好
You're not ready yet.
抱歉  把你手機摔了
I'm s... I'm sorry about your phone.
你應該買了保險吧
I'm sure you have the protection plan.
我確實有...
I do have the...
永遠不要買手機保險
Never get the protection plan!
大海非常瘋狂
The oceans are very wild.
任何人類  任何科技產品
No man or piece of scientific technology
都沒能到達過海底
has ever been to the bottom of the ocean.
-泰坦尼克號去過  -泰坦尼克沉了
- Titanic did. - Uh, Titanic sunk down there,
但是沒有沉到海底
but that's not to the bottom.
可是造泰坦尼克的人沉了
No, the man who made Titanic did.
尼克聽成了"Manwho"讓泰坦尼克沉到海底了
"蠻胡"是什么我不知道  但是...
I don't know what Manhoo is, but...
你們似乎比我嗨多了
You guys seem a lot higher than me.
每個人嗨的時間不一樣  伙計
Well, it hits everybody at different times, Hoss.
就快輪到你了
But it's coming for you.
伙伴們
My people!
打起精神來  我們要去參加派對啦
Time to rally, everybody. We are going to a party.
我接受了希希的建議
I took Cece's advice and decided to invite myself
決定和其他人一起去玩耍了
to hang out with some of the other guys,
我想你們也該一起去吧
and I think y'all should roll with.
讓我看起來更酷
Make me look cooler.
我會去參加在你屁股上開的派對的
I'll totally go to a party on your butt.
什么
What?
不
No. No.
那畫面真搞笑
Now, that is a humorous image.
什么
What?
-說真的  你們都得來  -不不不
- But, seriously, you have to go. - Oh, no, no, no, no.
我們會去的
You know what? We're gonna go.
We're gonna go.
-行  -我們會去的
- Okay. - We're gonna go.
我們會去的  我們會去的
We're gonna go. We're gonna go.
-你真的會去嗎  -我們會去的
- You're gonna go? - Hey, we're gonna go.
我們會去的
We're gonna go.
-我們會去的  -太好了
- We're gonna go. - Right on, right on.
我們會去的
Well, then we'll go.
你們都成這樣了還怎么去
You guys are way too messed up to be going.
你不在行  我可在行
You're not an expert. I am.
沒人會知道我們嗑嗨了
Nobody knows we're stoned.
要是我們不去  他們就會知道了
If we didn't go, then they would know.
你是說...
You're saying that be...
如果我們不去
if we don't go to the party,
他們就會知道我們嗑嗨了
they're gonna think that we're high.
你個從沒沾過大麻的家伙
Oh, the guy who's never done weed.
這說法不對  應該是"抽"大麻
That's not the proper term. It's "smoked weed."
不是"干掉"大麻  這個略難
You don't "do weed." That's a test.
-是你自己說的  -聽我說
- You said it. - Listen to me,
我們首先要做的是  吃掉他們的東西
first order of business, we eat their food.
-行  -然后你看著泳池說
- Okay. - Then you look at the pool.
"這泳池太贊了
"Aw, what a great pool.
我真想潛到水中一探究竟"
I wish... I wish I could dive for rings."
因為要是你嗑嗨了  就不會一潛究竟了
Because if you were stoned, you wouldn't dive for rings.
我在想這給人印象如何
Um, I was just thinking of this impression.
我在模仿誰
Who am I doing?
-我在模仿誰  -阿爾·帕西諾嗎
- Who am I doing? - Al Pacino?
美國著名演員
飾演《教父》中的邁克·柯里昂
也許吧  接著
Maybe. So, then,
你回屋  吃點比薩...
you get home, you eat some pizza...
相信我  我把可能在派對上發生的所有情況
Trust me. I just thought of every single possibility
都在腦海里過了一遍
of what could happen at that party,
沒一種是不好的
and none of them are bad.
這派對排場夠大的  到處都是警察
This is a big party. I'm talking wall-to-wall cops.
酷斃了
Man.
我還真沒考慮過這種情況
Oh, I did not think this through.
我覺得好嗨啊
It just hit me.
這就是為什么不論對方怎么連哄帶騙
And that is why-- no matter how tricked out it is--
你也不能上黑車
you never get into a van.
-"不上黑車"  -繼續
- "...van." - Moving on.
經典的危險警告
Classic warning signs.
要約你到他家附近碰面
said he needed to meet you near his house.
其實他的潛臺詞是
What he was really saying was,
"今晚我要跟你滾床單"
"I expect tonight to end in sex."
也有可能是他放不下他的寵物們
Or maybe he doesn't like to be far from his pets.
永遠不要跟養寵物的男人約會
Never date a man with pets.
男人要養寵物
The only acceptable pet
唯一能讓人接受的只有咸水魚
for a man to have is a saltwater fish. Okay, what now?
第一關  現在我要說一些話
Okay, first test. Now, I'm gonna say something,
你來說說我的言下之意是什么
and you tell me what's really being said.
我現在在賓館里待著呢
Oh, you know, I'm just staying in a hotel right now.
"我喜歡旅行"
"I like to travel."
沒有家室  變態
Homeless. Pervert.
天哪  我媽媽是最好的女人了
Oh, my God, my mom is just the most amazing woman.
"我愛我媽媽"
Oh. "I love my mother."
處男  也是個變態
Virgin. And somehow also a pervert.
我比較喜歡搭乘公共交通工具
I kind of prefer public transportation.
環保主義者
Oh. Earth-conscious.
經常酒駕
Multiple DUIs.
還是個變態
Pervert.
到下一關了
Okay, time for the next phase.
-下一關  -杰茜
- Next phase? - Jess?
我是馬爾科姆  搖約上約的
Hi. I'm Malcolm. From Dice?
-你好呀  -你好
- Oh, hi. - Hi.
-她一會兒就來找你  -好吧
- She'll be with you in just a minute. - Okay.
你給我安排了一個約會
You set me up on a date?
我就隨便穿了件內衣
I'm wearing my lounge-around underwear.
我給你安排了十個約會
I set you up on ten dates.
-什么  -一天內感受十年的體驗
- What? - Ten years of experience in one day.
約炮小能手
Expert by midnight.
搖約迪茲
The Dice Diez.
"迪茲"就是西班牙語里十個的意思
"Diez" Is Spanish for ten.
你瘋了嗎  施密特
Are you insane, Schmidt?
我還沒準備好
I'm not ready.
這就像把一出還在排練的音樂劇
That's like taking a musical from rehearsals
直接搬上百老匯一樣
straight to Broadway.
你得先去小地方試演一下
You got to workshop it first...
如果你有那么一丁點意思是
If you are for one second suggesting
說我不懂怎么給音樂劇開場...
that I don't know how to open a musical...
你怎么敢這么說  我是在幫你排憂解難
How dare you? I'm trying to help you out here.
你現在當然沒有準備好  杰茜
Now, of course you're not ready, Jess.
所以我才安排了十次約會
That's why I set up ten dates.
你可以的
Now, you can do this. Come on.
那好吧
All right.
-那么...  -相互了解一下吧
- So... - So. Date talk.
-好  -你是做什么的
- Okay. - What do you do?
我目前沒有工作
Um, well, I don't have a job, currently, right now,
沒有那種傳統的朝九晚五的工作
in the traditional "Nine to five" sense,
不過我經常煮各種好吃的
but, uh, I got a lot cooking.
我給別人種葡萄干
I "Grow" "Raisins."
不好意思  馬爾科姆
I'm sorry, Malcolm, um,
-我想...  -快過來
- I'm gonna have to... - Get out of there.
讓你接著說完
let you finish that story.
好的  我種了兩種葡萄干
Oh, okay. I grow two types of raisins.
有奧地利的
There's the Leopold raisin,
利奧波德葡萄干
which is from Austria.
還有茨維伯爾葡萄干
And then there's the Zwiebel raisin,
也是奧地利的品種
which is also from Austria.
不過我想讓我
But I think the main thing
幫助我熬過監獄時光的
that got me through my time in prison
就是明白了
was the realization
一顆葡萄干可以變成任何東西
that a "Raisin" can be anything.
我們該走了
We got to go!
老媽打電話來說蜜蜂回來了
Ma called. The bees are back.
好吧
Oh, okay. Um...
那我  那我用等你回來嗎
Should I just... Should I wait for you?
你知道那人不合適  對吧
You know that was a bad date, right?
我知道  但我覺得無法脫身
I know, but I just felt so trapped.
跟我學  找個借口離開就好了
Just do what I did, make up an excuse and then leave.
話越少越好  知道嗎
Just- just say as little as you need to, okay?
自己編個借口
Make it your own.
-你準備好了嗎  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
-你可以的  -好的
- You can do this. - Okay.
-你頭發真多  -什么
- You have so much hair. - What?
你怎么會有這么多頭發
Where did all that hair come from?
你看起來像只母獅子
You're like a lioness.
你知道你可以
So, did you know you could put
將一整只沒有拔毛或料理過的
a whole live chicken in your mouth and eat it
活雞放進嘴里然后吃掉嗎
without plucking it or preparing it at all?
簡明扼要
Keep it simple.
跟你直說吧
Uh, let's keep it simple.
你是個好人
You're a nice guy,
你的著裝也很整潔
and that's a neat outfit.
你是主廚嗎  還是"披頭族"
Are you a chef? Are you a beatnik?
你  你是在潛水艇里
Are... Do you work on...
工作嗎
on a submarine?
不  不
No! No!
放規矩點  先生
Stand down, sir!
我們找到你兒子了
We found your son.
他還活著
He's alive.
他們找到我兒子了  他還活著
They found my son; he's alive.
抱歉  見到你很高興
I'm sorry. It was nice meeting you.
好了  現在記住
All right, now, remember,
你們都是我的跟班  知道嗎
Y'all are my dogs, okay?
所以就站在我身邊
So just stay by my side
讓我看起來酷炫一點就好
and make me look cool.
我要是講笑話  你們要配合一下
If I tell a joke, dogs got to bark.
把你們的尾巴搖起來  知道嗎
I want to see those tails wagging out there, okay?
快看  快看
Oh, okay, look. Look,
那是杜根  杜根在那兒
there's Dugan. There's Dugan.
就是我跟你們說的那人  快來
That's the guy I was telling you about. Come on.
那邊看起來比較好
Over there is better.
好吧
All right.
-什么  -管她什么意思呢
- What? - Whatever the hell that means.
屋子里有警察嗎
Is there a cop in the house?
我覺得我現在很冷靜  很放松
I feel really calm. Really relaxed.
-看吶  蜂鳥  -你到底在說什么
- Oh, look, a hummingbird. - What the hell are you talking about?
根本就沒有什么蜂鳥
There's no such thing as a hummingbird.
鳥不會發出蜂鳴聲
Birds don't hum.
它們會唱歌
They sing.
唱歌就是它們創造出來的
They basically invented singing.
你現在太嗨了  兄弟
You're so high right now, man.
你太嗨了  我可能都沒法把你帶回去
You're so high, I couldn't possibly even bring you back.
事實上  兄弟  我感覺很好
Actually, dude, I feel really good.
你一走路
Hey, hey, hey, hey, when you walk,
看起來就像個瘋子
you look like an insane person.
-是嗎  -你聽起來像是嗑藥嗑嗨的瘋子
- Okay? - And your voice sounds so stoned and crazy.
說點什么
Say something.
你好  尼克
Hello, Nick.
你像是憋了二十分鐘才憋出來這句
That took you, like, 20 minutes.
"你好  尼克"
"Hello, Nick."
現在我在做模特和酒保
And now I'm a model and a bartender.
但我
But I...
我不確定之后做什么  我感覺有點迷惘
I'm not sure what's next. I feel a little lost.
我不太確定到底應該如何過我的人生
I'm not exactly sure what I'm doing with my life.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
再說一遍你的問題好嗎
What was your question again?
我什么都沒問你
I didn't ask you anything.
你自己走過來就開始說
You just walked up and started talking.
兄弟  我在更衣室
So, man, I'm in the locker room,
我看到一只蜘蛛  我就想
and I see a spider, and I'm like,
"我希望我在《夏洛特的網》里
"I hope this is Charlotte's Web
而你很友善”
and you're nice."
你們沒看過《夏洛特的網》嗎
You haven't seen Charlotte's Web?
《夏洛特的網》  卡通故事啊
Charlotte's Web, the, uh, cartoon.
關于一只非常冷淡非常酷的蜘蛛的故事
The tale about the spider who was super chill and super cool.
之后發生了一系列事  最后她死了
Then, well, series of events, she ended up dying.
所以這是個悲傷的故事
So that was sad.
很悲傷  但如果你們沒看過  我劇透了
That was sad, but spoiler alert, if you haven't seen it.
我肯定你們  你沒看過
I'm sure you... you haven't seen it.
我的跟班們呢
Where are my dogs?
我替你編了一些退場的臺詞
I took the liberty of writing down some exit lines,
因為很明顯你自己完全想不出來
because obviously, you can't come up with any on your own.
來  看看這些
Here, take a look at those.
我要去練冰球
I've got hockey practice?
-對  -我的老板想找我
- Sure. - My boss is trying to contact me
討論一個或許能拯救公司的項目
about a project that could save the company.
施密特
Schmidt,
這些很明顯就是拒絕的話
these are such obvious rejections.
我不想傷害他們的感情
I don't want to hurt their feelings.
傷害他們的感
Hurt their feel...
你每天都晃來晃去
Do you just walk around all day
考慮著別人的感受嗎
thinking about other people's feelings?
-對  你不是嗎  -不
- Yeah. Don't you? - No.
你是怎么做完任何事的
How do you get anything done?
-這很難  -好吧  杰茜
- It's hard. - Okay, Jess,
我該怎么說呢
how can I put this?
你才是大家需要爭奪的獎品
You're the prize here.
好嗎
Okay?
你就像最后一塊餡餅  而這些男人
You are the last piece of pie, and all of these guys
都是餐廳里的胖小孩
are the fat kids in the cafeteria,
我能這么說是因為我以前肥得跟卡車一樣
and I can say that because I used to be fat as a truck.
你真的覺得我是最后一塊餡餅嗎
You really think I'm the last piece of pie?
你當然是最后一塊餡餅
Damn right you're the last piece of pie.
你是搖約上最好的女孩  杰茜
You're the best girl on Dice, Jess.
誰在乎那些男的的感受
And who cares what these guys are feeling?
你感覺如何
You know, what do you feel?
杰茜  你想要什么
Jess, what do you want?
我是餡餅
I'm the pie.
-你是餡餅  -我是餡餅
- You're the pie. - I’m the pie.
-再說一遍  -我是餡餅
- Say it again. - I’m the pie.
就是這樣
There you go.
你是什么
Who are you?
還真沒想過這個
Never really thought about that.
我不是同性戀
I'm not gay,
但我超級愛麥克·史坎倫
but I would go crazy on Michael Strahan.
一位杰出的美國參議員想聯系我
A prominent U.S. Senator is trying to contact me.
我覺得梅麗爾·斯特里普就是個傻婊子
You know, I just think Meryl Streep is a dumb bitch.
有一份重要文件消失了
An important document has gone missing.
我得找到它
I need to find it.
我最近總和人打架
I've been getting into a lot of fist fights lately.
打了很多架
Like, a lot.
比以前頻繁的多
More than usual.
不過  不瞞你說
But, you know,
我現在有點上癮了
I'm kind of enjoying them now.
我有個熟人有危險
I have an acquaintance who's in jeopardy.
杰茜
Jess?
不  我不是杰茜
Nope, not Jess.
尼龍搭扣鞋  變態
Velcro shoes, pervert.
我都沒注意
I didn't even see those.
我希望你能分享
I would love for you to share...
分享
share...
你認為我這輩子該做什么
what you think I should do with my life.
你煩了嗎
Am I boring you now?
警官  我能告訴你們擁有的權利嗎
Officer, can I read you your rights?
你有權被人擁抱
You have the right to remain hugged.
不  教練
Oh, no, Coach!
而你有權繼續貼心
And you have the right to remain sweet.
跑  轉移
Run! Diversion!
-跑  快  -等等
- Run! Run! Now! Now! - Uh, du...? Whoa. Hold on!
你朋友們怎么回事  溫斯頓·貝肖普
What's with your friends, Winston Bishop?
他們踢翻了燒烤架  然后往那邊跑了
They kicked over the grill, and then they ran that way.
我知道
Yeah... I know.
最后一次約會
Wow. Last date.
這是值得紀念的時刻
It's a big moment.
我的天  那是我想的那個人嗎
Oh, my God, is that who I think it is?
介紹給你媚眼雅各布
I give you Dreamy Eyes Jacob.
搖約日開心  杰茜
Happy Dice birthday, Jess.
你已經準備好了  去釣他吧
You're ready for this. Now, go get him.
謝謝
Thank you, sir.
等等
Wait a minute.
你是波特蘭人嗎  衣服圖案是快樂牛奶
Are you from Portland? The Jolly Cow Creamery.
是的  我高中暑假在那里打過工
Yeah, I used to work there summers in high school.
-好巧  我也是波特蘭人  -真的嗎
- No way. I'm from Portland, too. - Are you serious?
我高中經常去那里
Yes. I used to go there all the time in high school.
-我天  -太有意思了
- Oh, my God. - That's so funny.
我希望你喜歡這里
Yeah, I hope you like this place.
我就住在街對面  所以
I live, like, right across the street, so...
我懂了
Oh. I get it.
你約我到這里是因為
You asked me here because
-想讓我去你家  -什么
- you want me to go home with you. - Wait. What?
我得走了
No. Um, you know what? I got to go.
我得去練冰球了
I have hockey practice.
我是中鋒  他們很需要我  我
I'm center wing, so they really need me. I...
我只是住在街對面
Okay, I just live across the street.
我可不是引誘你去我公寓干什么的變態
I'm not some weirdo trying to lure you back to my apartment.
我覺得我們很合得來
I thought we were kind of hitting it off.
看來你瞬間就做了決定
Guess you just make a snap decision,
就是這樣
and then that's it, so...
好了  訓練愉快
All right, well, have a good practice.
順便提一句  冰球沒有中鋒這個位置
And by the way, there's no center wing in hockey.
約會成功
The Dice Diez!
你做到了
You did it!
這東西好緊啊
This thing is on!
怎么打開啊
How do you open it?
這玩意兒居然不是香檳
Oh, wow. This isn't even champagne.
是一瓶特級的沙拉醬
Look, it's a super fancy salad dressing.
太好玩了
That is delightful.
我們要好好慶祝  就我和你
We are celebrating, me and you.
杰茜  你想點什么都成
Jess, you can have whatever you want on the menu.
這里有披薩  意式冰淇淋
They got pizza, gelato,
咖喱雞塊
tikka masala.
海鮮自助餐  這地方東西太雜了
A raw bar. This place is doing too much.
不可能每樣都好吃  你怎么了
They can't be doing all this right. What's wrong with you?
我就是不懂
I just don't understand how
我們今天學的東西怎樣能幫我找到真愛
what we did today is gonna help me find love.
真愛
Love?
你怎么會想要真愛呢
Well, why would you want to fall in love?
那我為什么要來約會啊
Why else would I go on dates?
拍拖的重點就在于可以一直拍拖下去啊
The point of dating is just to keep on dating,
永遠不停下
and then never stop.
就像是燒化石燃料或是看心理醫生
It's like burning fossil fuels or seeing a therapist.
不  施密特  去拍拖的重點
No. Schmidt, the whole point of going on dates
就是找到真愛  開始戀情
is to fall in love and have a relationship.
你都不糾結你是不是錯過了什么嗎
Like, don't you ever worry that you're missing out?
你耕耘過那么多女人
I mean, you're plowing through all these girls,
有些可能很不錯  但你永遠不會知道
and some of 'em might be great, but you'll never know.
你就想這樣過一生嗎
Do you want to go through life that way?
我想呀
Yeah.
但我不想
I don't.
我想要點一份...
Oh, hey, yeah. I'll take the, um...
巖蝦肉丸
the rock shrimp meatballs.
這地方到底是賣什么的
What is this place?
我覺得前途無望啊
I think my life is going nowhere.
希希  這才是最美的時候
No, Cece. It's wonderful here.
你喜歡學習嗎
Do you like to learn?
我喜歡
I do.
我覺得你可以重回學校深造
I see you going back to school.
-我也覺得  -是的  是的
- I see it, too. - Yes, yes.
-我不覺得  -是的
- I don't see it. - Yes.
她是個酒保  她怎么可能賺到錢
She's a bartender. Why would she get paid for it?
她還不太在行呢
She's not very good at it.
-趴下  -閉嘴
- On the floor! - Shut up!
抓住狗狗
Get the dog!
-趴下  快趴下  -別
- Get down on the ground! Yeah, and stay down! - No!
我只是個學生
I'm a student!
-你們倆  撅起屁股來  -我在努力
- Both of you, butts up. - I'm trying.
我很努力了
I'm trying.
我知道你們都嗑嗨了
See, I see you guys were high,
我就讓他們來整你們
so I got these guys to come and mess with you.
走了
Let's go, man.
我們不能再嗑藥了
Let's never do drugs again.
還挺好玩的  馬桶小弟
That was a lot of fun... Toilet.
馬桶小弟  這是我的綽號嗎
"Toilet." Is that... is that my nickname?
對啊  因為跟這群人住在一起
Yeah, 'cause living with these guys,
-你得忍受很多破事吧  -很多
- you got to put up with a lot of crap. - Lot of crap.
來喝啤酒吧
Let's get a beer.
太感謝你們了
Thank you very much.
沖沖  沖沖  為何如此匆匆
Flush, flush, what's the rush?
馬桶小弟來啦
Toilet's coming!
想鉆回壁櫥嗎
You guys want to go back in?
-想  -好
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-謝謝你能回來  -不客氣
- Thanks for coming back. - Sure.
聽著  我真的很抱歉
Look, I'm... I'm really sorry.
我都不知從哪說起了
Um, I was... I don't know where to begin.
我室友教了我
Uh, my roommate taught me all of these
那些虛假的借口  以便從約會中抽身
phony excuses to get out of dates.
反正  我不是那樣的人
Anyway, that is not me.
-好吧  -所以
- Okay. - So...
你愿意再給我一次機會來了解你嗎
will you give me another chance to get to know you?
愿意
Yeah.
我們再進去  喝點東西
Let's go back in and get a drink.
好  太棒了
Yes. Great.
你知道  我們可以讓上次約會徹底消失
Hey, uh, you know, we can just make that last date disappear.
就像  這枚硬幣
Like... this coin.
你是魔術師
You're a magician.
不  才不是呢
No. Ugh. No.
我是喜劇魔術師
I'm a comedy magician.
那更好了
Even better.
跟很多演喜劇的人一樣
And, like a lot of people in comedy,
我有點嗑藥的習慣
I have a little problem with, uh... nose candy.
這個不能給你  是我最后一個了
Can't have this. It's my last one.
不
No...
開玩笑的  送你
I'm kidding. Take it.
-我不想要  -請收下
- I don't want it. - Please take it.
不  你留著吧
No, you take it.
好吧  進去吧
Okay. Let's go in.
施密特
Schmidt?
我完全沒想到你會再聯系我
I totally didn't think I'd ever hear from you again.
我只是想到
Well, you know, I just figured,
如果我們之間有了真情  為什么不再見個面呢
why not see if there's something here?
你懂的  一起逛逛  加深了解
You know, let's hang out, get to know each other.
街上有家咖啡廳
There's a coffee place down the street
也許我們可以去那點杯咖啡
maybe we could go... grab a cup of Joe.
我覺得你不懂搖約的規則
I don't think you understand Dice.
好吧
Okay.
杰茜卡
Jessica!
我忘了去主持一個大人物的婚禮
I'm late to officiate a giant's wedding,
這倆環也解不開了
and these are stuck.
現在環解開了
Now the rings are free,
可新郎要永遠住在監獄里了
but the groom is imprisoned forever.
-我理解他們的感受  -你猜他們說什么
- I know how he feels. - You know what they say.
你得敲碎些雞蛋
You got to crack a few eggs to, uh...
來變出個阿米什人
make an Amish.
這是雞蛋
It's an egg.
雞蛋做的阿米什人
It's an Amish person.
我叔叔起火了
My uncle is on fire.
你見過從帽子里變出兔子的
So, you've seen a rabbit pulled out of a hat,
可你肯定沒見過  從兔子里變出帽子的
but have you ever seen a hat pulled out of a rabbit?
不  不
No, no!
天啊  夠了  約會結束
Oh, my... okay, this date is over.